http://www.ferrellcapital.com/privacy-policy

In the Media
Privacy PolicyFerrell Capital Management LLC ("the Firm") does not disclose any confidential personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law.The Firm will not disclose information outside of the exceptions and may include the following clause (or one largely similar to it) in its privacy statement:As part of Firm policy, it restricts access to confidential personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to its clients.  We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to comply with federal standards to guard your confidential personal information.”The Firm will ensure that this Privacy Policy is provided to new clients at the new account opening stage and that notice of its availability is also provided to the Firm’s customer statements on an annual basis.  Ferrell Capital Management LLC shares nonpublic information solely to service our client accounts. We may disclose the following information regarding clients and/or former clients, as necessary, to companies to perform certain services on our behalf or to other financial institutions, or as required by law:Information Ferrell Capital Management LLC receives from clients on applications (name, social security number, address, assets, etc.)Information about client transactions with Ferrell Capital Management LLC or others (account information, payment history, parties to transactions, etc.).Ferrell Capital Management LLC will internally safeguard your nonpublic personal information by restricting access to only those employees who provide products or services to you or those who need access to your information to service your account. In addition, we will maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that meet federal and/or state standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.
